adc.com 2019-12-14

# Privacy

### Privacy and Cookie Statement

Effective Date: May 25, 2018

This Privacy & Cookies Statement ("Privacy Statement") describes how CommScope, Inc. of North Carolina, located at 1100 CommScope Place SE, Hickory, North Carolina 28602, USA (the "Company" or "CommScope") collects, uses, shares, and otherwise processes individually identifiable data about visitors to this Site (defined below) as well as contact persons of our customers, prospects, distributors, sales representatives, vendors, investors, end users, and suppliers ("Personal Data"). This Privacy Statement applies to Personal Data that we collect through our public website (the "Site"), as well as offline through contact forms or other communications with CommScope personnel. 

### Summary of Key Points

 **1\. Collection**|  As a business to business (" **B2B** ") organization, we collect name, contact details, and other Personal Data related to our commercial relationships. Learn more >  
---|---  
 **2\. Use**|  We use Personal Data to provide our products and services and respond to inquiries, to manage accounts and maintain business operations, to provide relevant marketing, and to fulfill other business and compliance purposes. Learn more >  
 **3\. Sharing**|  We share Personal Data as necessary to provide our products and services and respond to requests, and to fulfill other business and compliance purposes. Learn more >  
 **4\. Marketing choices**|  You have control over how we use Personal Data for direct marketing. Learn more >  
 **5\. Cookies**|  We use cookies on our Site and in our communications, and provide choices on use of cookies, including third party targeting and advertising. Learn more >  
 **6\. Data subject rights**  | You have certain rights to request access, rectification, deletion, or other actions regarding your Personal Data where required by applicable law. Learn more >  
 **7\. Data security**|  We maintain technical and organizational measures to protect Personal Data from loss, misuse, alteration, or unintentional destruction. Learn more >  
 **8\. Cross-border data transfers**|  We provide appropriate protections for cross-border transfers where specified by law. Learn more >  
 **9\. Other issues**|  We provide other information in this Privacy Statement about: (i) the legal basis for collecting and processing Personal Data, (ii) the consequences for not providing Personal Data, (iii) automated decision-making, (iv) do-not-track (DNT) signals, (v) data retention, (vi) links to third-party websites, (vii) employee and contractor issues; and (viii) changes to this Privacy Statement. Learn more >  
 **10\. Contact us**|  Please contact us as detailed below with any questions. Learn more >  
  
* * *

#### 1\. Collection of Personal Data

We collect the following categories of Personal Data: 

**Basic Data** : Name, title, company, job responsibilities, phone number, mailing address, email address, and contact details. 

**Registration Data:** Newsletter requests, subscriptions, downloads, and username/passwords. 

**Device Data** : Computer Internet Protocol (IP) address, unique device identifier (UDID), cookies and other data linked to a device, and data about usage of our Site and communications (Usage Data). Note, however, we do not consider Device Data to be Personal Data except where we link it to you as an individual or where applicable law requires. 

**Marketing Data** : Data about individual participation in trade shows and conferences, credentials, associations, services or products you are interested in, and other preferences.

* * *

#### 2\. Use of Personal Data

We use the above categories of Personal Data for the following purposes:

 **Purpose of Use**

| 

 **Categories of Personal Data**  
  
---|---  
Provide the products and services you requested, respond to your inquiries, and allow CommScope to contact you.| Basic Data, Registration Data, and Device Data  
Manage your accounts, maintain our business operations, and allow you access to our proprietary systems.| Basic Data, Registration Data, and Device Data  
Make our Site more personal, intuitive and easy to use.| Device Data  
Protect the security and effective functioning of our Site and information technology systems.| Basic Data, Registration Data, and Device Data  
Provide relevant marketing about our or our affiliates' products and services, or promotions that we are developing, and opportunities that may be available to you.| Basic Data, Registration Data, Device Data, and Marketing Data  
Address our compliance and legal obligations and exercise our legal rights.| Basic Data, Registration Data, and Device Data  
  
* * *

#### 3\. Sharing of Personal Data

We share Personal Data with the following categories of recipients:

 **Affiliates:** We share Personal Data within the CommScope group of companies as necessary for the purposes we described above.

 **Service providers:** We share Personal Data with service providers to enable such parties to perform functions on our behalf and under our instructions in order to carry out the purposes identified above, such as marketing and web hosting. We require service providers to provide reasonable security for Personal Data and to use and process such Personal Data only on our behalf.

 **Auditors and advisors:** We share Personal Data with auditors for the performance of audit functions and advisors for the provision of legal and other advice.

 **Business reorganization:** We share Personal Data with any corporate purchaser or prospect to the extent permitted by law as part of any merger, acquisition, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider, as well as in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which Personal Data would be transferred as an asset of CommScope.

 **Mandatory disclosures and legal rights:** We share Personal Data in order to comply with any subpoena, court order or other legal process, or other governmental request.  We also share Personal Data to establish or protect our legal rights, property, or safety, or the rights, property, or safety of others, or to defend against legal claims.

If you have questions about the parties with which we share Personal Data, please contact us as specified below.

* * *

#### 4\. Marketing Choices

 **You have control regarding our use of your Personal Data for directing marketing.** If you no longer wish to receive any marketing communications, remain on a mailing list to which you previously subscribed, or receive any other marketing communication, **you can choose to not receive such communications at any time**. Please follow the unsubscribe link in the relevant communication, customize your communications in our Preference Center, or contact us as detailed below.

* * *

#### 5\. Cookies

We use and allow certain trusted partners to use cookies, web beacons, and similar tracking technologies (collectively, " **cookies** ") on our Site.

 ** _What are cookies?_**

Cookies are small amounts of data that are stored on your browser, device, communication, or the page you are viewing. Some cookies are deleted once you close your browser, while other cookies are retained even after you close your browser so that you can be recognized when you return to a websites. More information about cookies and how they work is available at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ "www.allaboutcookies.org").

 ** _How do we use cookies?_**

We use cookies to provide the Site, products, and services, gather information about your usage patterns when you navigate this Site in order to enhance your personalized experience, and to understand usage patterns to improve our Site, products, and services. We also allow certain trusted partners to place cookies on our Site in order to collect information about your online activities on our Site over time and across different websites you visit. This information is used to provide advertising tailored to your interests on websites you visit, also known as interest based advertising, and to analyze the effectiveness of such advertising.

Cookies on our Site are generally divided into the following categories:

 _Strictly Necessary Cookies_ : These are required for the operation of our Site. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas. These cookies are session cookies that are erased when you close your browser.

 _Analytical/Performance Cookies_ : These allow us to recognize and count the number of users of our Site and understand how such users navigate through our Site. This helps to improve how our Site works, for example, by ensuring that users can find what they are looking for easily. These cookies are session cookies, which are erased when you close your browser. We use Google Analytics, and you can see below for how to control the use of cookies by Google Analytics. 

_Functional Cookies_ : These improve the functional performance of our Site and make it easier for you to use. For example, cookies are used to remember that you have previously visited the Site and asked to remain logged into it. These cookies qualify as persistent cookies, because they remain on your device for us to use during a next visit to our Site. You can delete these cookies via your browser settings.

 _Targeting Cookies_

: These record your visit to our Site, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed to recognize you as a previous visitor and to track your activity on the Site and other websites you visit. These cookies qualify as persistent cookies, because they remain on your device for us to use during a next visit to our Site. You can delete these cookies via your browser settings. See below for further details on how you can control third party targeting cookies.

 ** _What are your options if you do not want cookies on your computer?_**

You can review your Internet browser settings, typically under the sections "Help" or "Internet Options," to exercise choices you have for certain Cookies. If you disable or delete certain Cookies in your Internet browser settings, you might not be able to access or use important functions or features of this Site, and you may be required to re-enter your log-in details.

To learn more about the use of cookies for Google analytics and to exercise choice regarding such cookies, please visit [ https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout " https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout").

To learn more about certain cookies used for interest based advertising by third parties, including through cross-device tracking, and to exercise certain choices regarding such cookies, please visit the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/ "Digital Advertising Alliance"), [Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/ "Network Advertising Initiative"), [Digital Advertising Alliance-Canada](http://youradchoices.ca/choices "Digital Advertising Alliance-Canada"), [European Interactive Digital AdvertisingAlliance](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/ "European Interactive Digital AdvertisingAlliance") or your device settings.

* * *

#### 6\. Data Subject Rights

Where required by applicable law, you have the right to obtain confirmation that we maintain certain Personal Data relating to you, to verify its content, origin, and accuracy, as well as the right to access, review, port, delete, or to block or withdraw consent to the processing of certain Personal Data (without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal), by contacting us through the [**Act On YourPersonal Data**](http://www.commscope.com/gdprrequest "Act On YourPersonal Data") feature.   **In particular, you have the right to object to our use of Personal Data for direct marketing and in certain other situations at any time.   Contact us below for more details. ** Please note that we need to retain certain Personal Data as required or permitted by applicable law. 

* * *

#### 7\. Data Security

We maintain technical and organizational measures to protect Personal Data from loss, misuse, alteration, or unintentional destruction. However, no security measure can guarantee against compromise. You also have an important role in protecting your Personal Data. You should not share your username and password with anyone, and you should not re-use passwords across more than one website. If you have any reason to believe that your username or password has been compromised, please contact us as detailed below.

* * *

#### 8\. Cross-Border Data Transfers

We transfer Personal Data to various jurisdictions as necessary for the purposes described above, including to jurisdictions that may not provide the same level of data protection as your home country. We provide appropriate protections for cross-border transfers as required by law for international data transfers. With respect to transfers originating from the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "), we implement standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission, and other appropriate solutions to address cross-border transfers as required by applicable law. Where required by such laws, you may request a copy of the suitable mechanisms we have in place by contacting us as detailed below.

* * *

#### 9\. Other Issues

 ** _(i) What is the legal basis of processing?_**

Some jurisdictions require an explanation of the legal basis for the collection and processing of Personal Data. We have several different legal grounds on which we collect and process Personal Data, including: (a) as necessary to perform a transaction (such as in order to provide the products and services you requested); (b) as necessary to comply with a legal obligation (such as when we use Personal Data for record keeping to substantiate tax liability); (c) consent (where you have provided consent as appropriate under applicable law, such as for direct marketing or certain cookies); and (d) necessary for legitimate interests (such as when we act to maintain our business generally, including maintaining the safety and security of the Site). With respect to legitimate interests, given that we are a B2B company, we typically collect and process limited Personal Data about customer contacts and other individuals acting in their business capacities, as part of our overall effort to reduce the privacy impact on individuals.

 ** _(ii) What are the consequences of not providing Personal Data?_**

You are not required to provide all Personal Data identified in this Privacy Statement to use our Site or to interact with us offline, but certain functionality will not be available if you do not provide certain Personal Data. If you do not provide certain Personal Data, we may not be able to respond to your request, perform a transaction with you, or provide you with marketing that we believe you would find valuable.

 ** _(iii) Do we engage in automated decision-making without human intervention?_**

We do not use automated decision-making without human intervention, including profiling, in a way that produces legal effects concerning you or otherwise significantly affects you.

 ** _(iv) Does the Site honor do not track ("DNT") signals sent via browsers?_**

Given the divergent practices of organizations that offer browsers and the lack of a standard in the marketplace, we do not respond to DNT signals at this time.

 ** _(v) How long do we retain Personal Data?_**

We typically retain Personal Data related to marketing activities for as long as you accept marketing communications from us, and upon request we will securely delete such data in accordance with applicable law. For Personal Data that we collect and process for other purposes described above, we typically retain such Personal Data for no longer than for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement and as otherwise needed to address tax, corporate, compliance, litigation, and other legal rights and obligations.

 ** _(vi) Are third-party websites governed by this Privacy Statement?_**

This Site contains links and references to other websites administered by unaffiliated third parties. This Privacy Statement does not apply to such third party websites. When you click a link to visit a third party websites, you will be subject to that website's privacy practices. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy and security practices of the linked third party websites before providing any Personal Data on that website.

 ** _(vii) How does CommScope handle employee and contractor privacy issues?_**

Personal Data about our employees, contractors, and other CommScope temporary workers are addressed through internal company policies and procedures, and are outside the scope of this Privacy Statement.

 ** _(viii) How will we handle any changes to this Privacy Statement?_**

We may update this Privacy Statement from time to time as our services and privacy practices change, or as required by law. The effective date of our Privacy Statement is posted above, and we encourage you to visit our Site periodically to stay informed about our privacy practices. We will post the updated version of the Privacy Statement on our Site, and ask for your consent to the changes if legally required.

* * *

#### 10\. Contact Us

If you have questions or comments regarding this Privacy Statement or our privacy practices, please contact us at:

 **CommScope, Attn: Legal Department  
1100 CommScope Place SE, Hickory, NC, 28602  
Email: [privacycontact@commscope.com](mailto:privacycontact@commscope.com?subject=Request%20from%20Website "Request from Website")**

CommScope's Data Protection Officer for Germany can be contacted at:

datenschutz süud GmbH  
Wörthstraße 15  
97082 Würzburg, Germany

 _You may also have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant data protection supervisory authority._
